{
    "id": "cb5c4081f3214e1d8c92945975034a62",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The police busted the gang by acting ............................. tips from an informer.",
            "description": "To act on is to take action on the basis of information received.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "after",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The children acted ................................ the story of Cinderella on stage.",
            "description": "To act out is to perform with actions and gestures.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The children act .................................. whenever we have guests.",
            "description": "To act up is to behave badly.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Their explanations just do not add ......................................",
            "description": "When things add up, they make sense.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Cold weather does not agree .................................. me.",
            "description": "If something does not agree with you, it has a negative impact on you.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Most commercials of fast foods are aimed ....................................... children.",
            "description": "To aim at is to target.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Their children are badly brought up. They answer their parents ...............................",
            "description": "To answer back is to reply rudely to an elderly person.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "back",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can never argue my wife ...............................",
            "description": "To argue somebody down is to beat them in an argument.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "James called in the morning to ask .................................. you.",
            "description": "To ask after somebody is to enquire about their health",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "out",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They have asked us ................................. for dinner on Sunday.",
            "description": "To ask somebody over is to invite them.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "over",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The police ordered the rioters to back ..................................",
            "description": "To back off is to retreat.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She backed ...................................... the promise at the last minute",
            "description": "To back out of a promise is to fail to keep it.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "out of",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}